https://uumarin.org/website-privacy-policy/

Website Privacy Policy - Unitarian Universalist Congregation of Marin
Skip to content
Search for:
Search
Google Map
Something went wrong while retrieving your map.
Contact us!
Unitarian Universalist Congregation of Marin
Inspiring joy and justice in an imperfect world.
Adult Education
Young Adults (18+)
Pastoral Care
Volunteer!
Website Privacy Policy
This policy is pending approval by the Board.
This website is owned and operated by the Unitarian Universalist Congregation of Marin, referred to in this policy as “we”. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This privacy policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: office@uumarin.org
We are available to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
The first principle of Unitarian Universalism is to covenant to affirm and promote the inherent worth and dignity of every person. We believe that this principle impels us to protect the privacy of visitors.
Personal Information
Our site collects personal information from our visitors only on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name or other identifying information  .We do not require this information to obtain access to any part of our site. We do not sell or rent this personal information to other organizations.
The personal information we collect is only used by us to process a request that has been placed by the visitor. We never sell your email address and if you voluntarily give it to us, we will strive to use it only for what it was intended. If we pass it, it would only be to the congregation or person who has the information you desire.
Statistical Information Collected
We collect information on the browsing habits of users and the companies that provide that service also have access to that information. This site collects information using cookies and javascript, so if they are enabled in your browser, information can be collected, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address, and country. This information is only used for statistical purposes and cannot identify you as an individual.
Information Accuracy
We make every effort to ensure that the information presented is correct and accurate. If inaccuracies occur, we will make every effort to correct them in a timely manner. To report any web site inaccuracies or for questions about our Privacy Policy please email us at webmaster@uumarin.org .
Links to Third Party Sites
Our web sites contain some hyperlinks to web sites operated by parties other than the UU Congregation of Marin. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference only. We do not control such web sites and are not responsible for their contents or privacy policies. The inclusion of hyperlinks to other web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on these Web sites or any association with their operators.
Section Navigation
Recent Posts
Update on the Auction
October 2, 2020
Flaming Chalice Masks For Sale
September 3, 2020
Meet Our New Religious Exploration Staff!
August 28, 2020
Help the Street Chaplaincy Program
July 21, 2020
Instructions on Making Pledge Payments and other donations
June 26, 2020
Upcoming Church Events
Sat, 10 Oct 20209:00 am Saturday CircleSun, 11 Oct 20209:00 am Sunday Circle9:30 am 1st grade to 5th grade Children's Gathering10:30 am Sunday Worship Service12:00 pm 6th to 9th Grade Youth Gathering- Zoom 212:00 pm Congregational Meeting12:30 pm Soul Matters GroupMon, 12 Oct 20207:00 pm Soul Matters Group - Non-UUCM Zoom AccountTue, 13 Oct 20203:00 pm Executive Committee7:00 pm Choir Rehearsal - Non-UUCM Zoom AccountWed, 14 Oct 202010:00 am Soul Matters Group12:00 pm Theology Over Lunch with Rev. Marcus1:30 pm Classic Book Club5:00 pm Tech Committee6:30 pm Crafting for a Cause - ZoomThu, 15 Oct 20201:00 pm Thursday Monthly Small Group Ministry1:30 pm Soul Matters GroupSat, 17 Oct 20209:00 am Saturday CircleSun, 18 Oct 20209:00 am Sunday Circle9:30 am 1st grade to 5th grade Children's Gathering10:30 am Sunday Worship Service12:00 pm 6th to 9th Grade Youth Gathering- Zoom 212:00 pm Social Justice Committee Meeting12:15 pm Soul Matters GroupMon, 19 Oct 202010:00 am UUCM Auction Planning MeetingTue, 20 Oct 202011:00 am Nominating Committee Meeting3:00 pm Stewardship Committee7:00 pm Choir Rehearsal - Non-UUCM Zoom AccountWed, 21 Oct 202012:00 pm Theology Over Lunch with Rev. Marcus12:30 pm Men's Group2:30 pm Finance Committee5:00 pm Tech CommitteeFri, 23 Oct 202010:30 am Soul Matters Group1:00 pm Soul Matters Group7:30 pm Remarkable People: FridaySat, 24 Oct 20209:00 am Saturday CircleSun, 25 Oct 20209:00 am Sunday Circle9:30 am 1st grade to 5th grade Children's Gathering10:30 am Sunday Worship Service12:00 pm 6th to 9th Grade Youth Gathering- Zoom 2Tue, 27 Oct 20207:00 pm Choir Rehearsal - Non-UUCM Zoom AccountWed, 28 Oct 202012:00 pm Theology Over Lunch with Rev. Marcus5:00 pm Tech Committee6:30 pm Crafting for a Cause - ZoomThu, 29 Oct 20206:00 pm Board MeetingSat, 31 Oct 20209:00 am Saturday CircleSun, 1 Nov 20209:00 am Sunday Circle9:30 am 1st grade to 5th grade Children's Gathering10:30 am Sunday Worship Service12:00 pm 6th to 9th Grade Youth Gathering- Zoom 2Mon, 2 Nov 202010:00 am UUCM Auction Planning MeetingTue, 3 Nov 202010:30 am Pastoral Care Committee7:00 pm Choir Rehearsal - Non-UUCM Zoom AccountWed, 4 Nov 202012:00 pm Theology Over Lunch with Rev. Marcus12:30 pm Men's Group5:00 pm Tech CommitteeThu, 5 Nov 20203:00 pm Worship Associates MeetingSat, 7 Nov 20209:00 am Saturday CircleSun, 8 Nov 20209:00 am Sunday Circle9:30 am 1st grade to 5th grade Children's Gathering10:30 am Sunday Worship Service12:00 pm 6th to 9th Grade Youth Gathering- Zoom 212:30 pm Soul Matters Group
Contact us!
NewsletterVisitors: Sign up for our weekly eNewsletter today!
Member LoginPlease login using your e-mail address and password.
Forgot your password?
